Mahmoud Alakhal

Civil Engineer & senior site engineer

About Mahmoud Alakhal a civil engineer with more than four years of experience as a site engineer, good in analysis, planning, implementation and dealing with many difficult cases. Holding a valid UAE Driver's License. I can speak English and Urdu beside my native Arabic



alakhalmahmoud5@gmail.com

0097561374291

Dubai - UAE, Syria

linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-alakhal- in 29a663193

facebook.com/mahmoud alakhal

G

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Site EngineerBin Odeh Building Contracting LLC

10/2021 - Present

Dubai, UAE

Proiects

- G+1 villa+roof al warqa third plot NO:4238268
- G+1 villa+roof al warga third plot NO:4238267
- G+1 +roof luxuries villa in al mizhar first third plot NO:2620546
- B+G+1 palac Emirate hills (L22)

Site Engineer

Reem Capital Contracting LLC

07/2019 - 09/2021

Dubai, UAE

Proiects

- Al ANDALUS Tower (G+4P+12+ROOF)+complexed car parking+related club house By Jumeirah Golf Estate.
- ANWA- Tower (G+4P+44+ROOF) By Omniyat.

Site Enginner

Al Sayed Contracting Comapny

06/2017 - 04/2019

Lattakia, Syrai

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Structure in Civil Engineering Tishreen University Lattakia, Syria

Year graduated: July 2019 , GPA: 72.2 % , Rating: Very Good

Equivalency of Certificate MOE, UAE.

RESPONSIBILITIES

Inspections, Quality Control, Follow Up Planned Schedule

BBS Preparation, Review, Check, and Request Order

Subcontractors interim payments verification

Manage Project Activities

Cost control

Prepare Daily Reports

Request Materials

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Urdu

Professional Working Proficiency

AREAS OF KNOWLEDGE

Close coordination on site logistics and deliverables with all stakeholders, subcontractors etc.

Analyses engineering drawings and specifications to plan layout, coordination on site requirements.

Coordinate on joinery installation and assist in managing the works on site

Supervise the work regularly, provide on the spot guidance to ensure high quality craftsmanship and keep senior production supervisor posted on the progress of site works.

Being able to manage staff working hours with maximum efficiency and high performance.

Labour and material handling and management.

Site inspections and coordination between QC and Consultant.

Concrete pouring and supervision.

Project handing over, snagging and de snagging works.

Building maintenance works.